

THAJANAH MAILVAGANAM

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

Objective

To obtain an intern/junior position in the digital platforms team where I can apply my technical skills and contribute to building innovative digital products.

About me

I have a basic understanding of software development and programming languages. I have a strong passion for creating. I have experience integrating APIs and am familiar with HTML5, CSS, NODE.JS, and REACT.JS. I have a self-motivated attitude toward learning new technologies and excellent teamwork and problem-solving skills.

Technical Skills

- Strong understanding of HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, and React JS
- Familiar with MongoDB
- Ability to communicate effectively both verbally and in writing
- Self-motivated to learn new technologies and applications
- Excellent problem-solving skills
- Strong teamwork and collaboration skills

Education

CONCORDIA UNIVERSITY

Full-Stack Web Development

- Build full-stack applications
- Build mobile-first responsive websites
- Build UI components using React JS
- Collaborate with other developers
- Deliver individual projects according to deadlines
- Work on both frontend and backend components

BCOM Finance 2019-2021

- Learned to read financial statements
- Grew a better understanding of marketing and design

DAWSON COLLEGE

Pure and Applies Sciences

- Grew interested in biology and sustainability
- Enjoyed problem solving

Certificates

In the process of completing a Figma certificate

Projects

E-COMMERCE SITE

- built an understanding of how to use Visual Studio code for collaborative work
- use git commands
- assisted my teammates in reviewing the code

Frontend Component:

- Build UI components using React JS
- Made attractive-seamless designs
- Contributed to the development of brainstorming web page ideas

Backend Component:

- Updating stock to MongoDB
- Implemented REST API practice

Saree Draping Service - Booking Site (Personal Project)

• Used AuthO API for user login

Frontend component:

- Built a calendar from scratch
- Build UI components using React JS
- users can book the date and view all bookings

Backend component:

- user data is saved to MongoDB
- use REST API practice to view/edit booking details.

Work Experience

FUJITSU SERVICE DESK | JAN 2023-PRESENT

- Assist users with troubleshooting/debugging
- Strong communication and interpersonal skills, both verbal and written
- Ability to multitask and prioritize tasks effectively
- · Good problem-solving and analytical skills
- Good understanding of computer systems and software

IKEA | 2019-PRESENT

- Answered general inquiries about store operation
- Promoted 2020 to Resolution Agent position
- Good problem-solving and analytical skills
- Good attention to detail and follow-through skills
- Strong communication and interpersonal skills, both verbal and written

TUTORING MATH | 2016 & 2019 & 2022

- Ability to explain complex concepts in a clear and concise manner
- Prepared effective study plans to help them achieve their academic goals.